[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Army", "Army"]}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "When you were here as a young, fresh-faced Colin Powell, what was the big dream for you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "here", "as", "a", "young", ",", "fresh-faced", "Colin", "Powell", ",", "what", "was", "the", "big", "dream", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "I was doing a lieutenant colonel and I was doing fairly well in the Army, but I had no idea what the Army had in store for me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "doing", "a", "lieutenant", "colonel", "and", "I", "was", "doing", "fairly", "well", "in", "the", "Army", ",", "but", "I", "had", "no", "idea", "what", "the", "Army", "had", "in", "store", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin Powell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "You as we sit here on Veterans Day in particular, what do you feel about the view of the modern American military?", "question_tokens": ["You", "as", "we", "sit", "here", "on", "Veterans", "Day", "in", "particular", ",", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "view", "of", "the", "modern", "American", "military", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNPS", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "It's a great military.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "great", "military", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Do you feel that you need another Gerald Ford intervention?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "you", "need", "another", "Gerald", "Ford", "intervention", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Somebody will show up.", "answer_tokens": ["Somebody", "will", "show", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gerald Ford"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What advice would you give him to get America back on its feet right now in the modern world?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "him", "to", "get", "America", "back", "on", "its", "feet", "right", "now", "in", "the", "modern", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, you know, you can't put it all on one individual.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "put", "it", "all", "on", "one", "individual", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Why is it not happening?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "it", "not", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "It's not happening now because it's been made too difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "happening", "now", "because", "it", "'s", "been", "made", "too", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "You're going to blame me, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "going", "to", "blame", "me", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "No, I'm not blaming you.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "blaming", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Would you take that approach?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "take", "that", "approach", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Well, I don't play golf, so I wouldn't have got on the golf course.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "play", "golf", ",", "so", "I", "would", "n't", "have", "got", "on", "the", "golf", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Can you clarify that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "clarify", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I means go hide in your -- in your bunker so that people can't get to you, and then come out and fight in the streets.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "means", "go", "hide", "in", "your", "--", "in", "your", "bunker", "so", "that", "people", "ca", "n't", "get", "to", "you", ",", "and", "then", "come", "out", "and", "fight", "in", "the", "streets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "What do you think you should be advising him as someone who supported him about how to go back into the election fray?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "you", "should", "be", "advising", "him", "as", "someone", "who", "supported", "him", "about", "how", "to", "go", "back", "into", "the", "election", "fray", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Well, the advice I'd give to the president, which I still do on occasion, I keep private.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "advice", "I", "'d", "give", "to", "the", "president", ",", "which", "I", "still", "do", "on", "occasion", ",", "I", "keep", "private", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Where were you when you heard that bin Laden had been killed?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "you", "heard", "that", "bin", "Laden", "had", "been", "killed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I was in my home, and I heard the news.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "in", "my", "home", ",", "and", "I", "heard", "the", "news", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Did you admire the president for the sheer audacity of the decision-making of that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "admire", "the", "president", "for", "the", "sheer", "audacity", "of", "the", "decision-making", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CD", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "The huge difference in cost not just in human life but financially to America?", "question_tokens": ["The", "huge", "difference", "in", "cost", "not", "just", "in", "human", "life", "but", "financially", "to", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I don't think the two can be that easily compared.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "the", "two", "can", "be", "that", "easily", "compared", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "I mean do you feel that you were in some way used?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "do", "you", "feel", "that", "you", "were", "in", "some", "way", "used", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "What do you make of it all?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "It's a remarkable democratic system we have.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "remarkable", "democratic", "system", "we", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "I mean are you watching it as a Democrat or Republican?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "are", "you", "watching", "it", "as", "a", "Democrat", "or", "Republican", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I'm watching it as an American.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "watching", "it", "as", "an", "American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "If the election was tomorrow, and it will be in a year, and would you vote for Barack Obama as things stand again?", "question_tokens": ["If", "the", "election", "was", "tomorrow", ",", "and", "it", "will", "be", "in", "a", "year", ",", "and", "would", "you", "vote", "for", "Barack", "Obama", "as", "things", "stand", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I would never make that decision now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "never", "make", "that", "decision", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "You think more may pop up?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "more", "may", "pop", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "I mean could we possibly see yourself?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "could", "we", "possibly", "see", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "I rejected that 16 years ago, and I've given more than one explanation for it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "rejected", "that", "16", "years", "ago", ",", "and", "I", "'ve", "given", "more", "than", "one", "explanation", "for", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Are you really?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Was it your wife in the end who decided?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "your", "wife", "in", "the", "end", "who", "decided", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "It was me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "It was you, not your wife?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "you", ",", "not", "your", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Am I a good shrink or bad shrink?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "a", "good", "shrink", "or", "bad", "shrink", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Stick to being on television.", "answer_tokens": ["Stick", "to", "being", "on", "television", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Are you more moderate by nature?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "more", "moderate", "by", "nature", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Cain", "Herman"]}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "What do you make of Herman Cain?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "Herman", "Cain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I've known Mr. Cain for -- oh, I guess, known Herman for 15, 16 years.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "known", "Mr.", "Cain", "for", "--", "oh", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "known", "Herman", "for", "15", ",", "16", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Is it the man you recognize with all these claims?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "the", "man", "you", "recognize", "with", "all", "these", "claims", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I'm not going to get in to all of these claims.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "get", "in", "to", "all", "of", "these", "claims", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Do you remember that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vietnam"]}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "How did you get out of that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "get", "out", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "We didn't have any money and I was going to Vietnam.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "did", "n't", "have", "any", "money", "and", "I", "was", "going", "to", "Vietnam", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Where do you get this from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "get", "this", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "No, I'm just --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "just", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "What's the secret of a happy marriage?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "secret", "of", "a", "happy", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Getting along.", "answer_tokens": ["Getting", "along", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "TO", "NNS", ",", "NN", "TO", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What are the key values to you that you think most people should really have as priorities?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "key", "values", "to", "you", "that", "you", "think", "most", "people", "should", "really", "have", "as", "priorities", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "OWELL: Service to others, service to something greater than yourself, service to country, serving a purpose in life.", "answer_tokens": ["OWELL", ":", "Service", "to", "others", ",", "service", "to", "something", "greater", "than", "yourself", ",", "service", "to", "country", ",", "serving", "a", "purpose", "in", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What were your parents have made of your career?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "your", "parents", "have", "made", "of", "your", "career", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Well, they were proud of me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "were", "proud", "of", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Do you really?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harlem"]}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Do you think they're misguided?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "they", "'re", "misguided", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Well, I was -- I was born in Harlem to immigrant parents, and my parents always had a job.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "--", "I", "was", "born", "in", "Harlem", "to", "immigrant", "parents", ",", "and", "my", "parents", "always", "had", "a", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "How do we get businesses that have a lot of money stacked up, how do we get them to invest that money and create jobs?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "get", "businesses", "that", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "stacked", "up", ",", "how", "do", "we", "get", "them", "to", "invest", "that", "money", "and", "create", "jobs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "RP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "You said before with foreign policy that America should avoid saying we are going to instill our democracy on everybody.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "said", "before", "with", "foreign", "policy", "that", "America", "should", "avoid", "saying", "we", "are", "going", "to", "instill", "our", "democracy", "on", "everybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJS", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "When you look back on it, excluding the obvious, children's births and marriage and so on, what's the single greatest moment of your life?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "on", "it", ",", "excluding", "the", "obvious", ",", "children", "'s", "births", "and", "marriage", "and", "so", "on", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "single", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I never answer single greatest or worst a questions.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "answer", "single", "greatest", "or", "worst", "a", "questions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "What message would you give them on this particular day?", "question_tokens": ["What", "message", "would", "you", "give", "them", "on", "this", "particular", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "I'm so enormously proud of all of those who are serving now and all of those who served in the past.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "so", "enormously", "proud", "of", "all", "of", "those", "who", "are", "serving", "now", "and", "all", "of", "those", "who", "served", "in", "the", "past", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]